Guide to the American Wind Symphony Orchestra Records, 1957-2012 AIS.1981.19
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publicity, 1959-2012; VII.
  - Press Releases and Announcements, 1959-1985; 4.
    - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Press Releases, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbooks, 1960-1961; 5.
    This subseries contains scrapbooks made in the 1960s for the American Wind Symphony Orchestra for the years 1960-1961. The scrapbooks contain mostly copies of newspaper, and magazine clippings about the orchestra or the orchestra's concerts.
    - Scrapbook, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Educational Programs, Festivals, and Other Projects, 1962-1988; VIII.
  This series contains information about special events, educational programs, and festivals organized by the American Wind Symphony Orchestra. Most notably, this series has documentation on the Floating Center of the Arts barge project, Pennsylvania Artist Exhibition, and the AWSO's Caribbean Scholar Program. The content of folders is varied, but folders generally contain correspondence, invitations, photographs, flyers, pamphlets, press releases, and handwritten notes. This series is arranged chronologically by year.
  - Nigerian Orchestra Symposium, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - American Wind Youth Orchestra (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Third Annual Jazz Festival, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Symposium, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Teenage 66, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cultural Exchange Program, No Date (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Black Arts Festival, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - American Waterways Floating Center of the Arts, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - American Waterways Floating Center of the Arts, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Symphony South, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cultural Enrichment Program, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bicentennial Odyssey, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Floating Center of the Arts Barge Project, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Floating Center of the Arts Barge Project, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Floating Center of the Arts Barge Project, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Tea Party, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - High School Arts Exhibition, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Poetry Symposium, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Theatre, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Theatre, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Floating Center of the Arts, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Floating Center of the Arts, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Scandinavian Festival, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Seats in the Park, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - International Competition, 1979-1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Dock Dinner, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Journey with the Arts, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Access Transportation System, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania Artists Exhibit, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania Artists Exhibit, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania Artists Exhibit, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Wind Orchestra of the Americas, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Wind Orchestra of the Americas, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Wind Orchestra of the Americas, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Wind Orchestra of the Americas, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Senior Citizens Program, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Caribbean Scholar Program, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Caribbean Scholar Program, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Caribbean Scholar Program, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Landmark Benefit, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Meet the Composer, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rico Youth Wind Orchestra, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Worlds Fair, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The Great Fish Tale, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Statue of Liberty Rededication, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Solo Trombone Competition and Symposium, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Bicentennial Project, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Jazz Improvisation Festival, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Institute of the American Wind Symphony Orchestra, No Date (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Family Theatre, No Date (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Concerts and Tours, 1959-1988; IX.
  This series contains records about American Wind Symphony Orchestra's performances and tours from the 1960s until the 1980s, as well as correspondence discussing the possibility of concerts with local governments, businesses, and civic groups. There are folders that pertain to entire tours, and other folders that contain information, correspondence, publicity, and other records from locations at which the AWSO played, including locations in the United States, Canada, Central America, and the Caribbean. Folders contain correspondence, budget documents, handwritten notes, AWSO member lists, lists of performing locations, maps, schedules, newspaper clippings, pamphlets and programs. Folders pertaining to tours have been arranged chronologically, while folders about individual cities are arranged alphabetically.
  - Tour, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Tour, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Tour, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Tour, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Tour, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Tour, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Tour, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Tour, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Tour, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Tour, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Tour, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Tour, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Tour, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Tour, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Tour, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Tour, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Tour, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Tour, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Tour housing, 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Aberdeen, MS, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Albany, NY, 1982-1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Alcoa, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Alexandria, VA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Allegheny County, PA, 1979-1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Allegheny County, PA, 1979-1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Alpena, MI, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Annapolis, MD, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Amsterdam, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Apalachicola, FL, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Bainbridge, GA, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Barbados, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Baton Rouge, LA, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Bay City, MI, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Beaufort, CT, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Beaumont, TX, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Beaver, PA, 1964-1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Bethel Park, PA, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Beckley, WV, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Biloxi, MS, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Boston, MA, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Bradenton, FL, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Bridgeville, PA, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Bristol, PA, 1982-1986 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Brockville, OH, No Date (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Burlington, LA, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - California, PA, No Date (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Colombia, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Caribbean Trip, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Caribbean Trip, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Caribbean Trip, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Carrick (Pittsburgh), PA, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Cincinnati, OH, 1982-1988 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Charleroi, PA, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Charleston, SC, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Charleston, WV, 1970-1984 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Chattahoochee, FL, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Chattanooga, TN, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Cheboygan, MI, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Chicago, IL, 1975-79 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Clarksville, TN, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Clinton, IA, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Clyde, NY, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Cocoa, FL, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Conneaut, OH, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Coudersport, PA, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Corpus Christi, TX, 1973-1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Costa Rica, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Curacao, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Delaware County, PA, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Demopolis, AL, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Detroit, MI, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Dominican Republic, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Dubuque, IA, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Duluth, MN, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Dunkirk, NY, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - East Coast, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - East End (Pittsburgh, PA), 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - East Liverpool, OH, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth, PA, 1968-1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Erie, PA, 1964-1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Escanaba, MI, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Etna/Sharpsburg, PA, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Evanston, IL, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Evansville, IN, 1965-1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Fairmont, WV, 1963-1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Fall River, MA, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Frankfort, KY, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Florence, AL, 1965-1987 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Ft. Lauderdale, FL, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Ft. Myers, FL, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Ft. Pierce, FL, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Ft. Smith, AR, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Fulton, NY, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Gallipolis, OH, 1966-1988 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Galveston, TX, 1973-1982 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Gary, IN, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Great Lakes, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Great Lakes Tour, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Green Bay, WI, 1964-1983 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Greensburg, PA, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Greenville, MS, 1962-1988 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Greenwich, CT, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Guatemala, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Haiti, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hampton, PA, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hannibal, MO, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Hartford, CT, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Henderson, KY, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hilton Head, SC, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Helena, AR, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Holland German Tour, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Holland, MI, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Hollywood, FL, 1967-1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Homestead, PA, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Homewood (Pittsburgh), PA, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Honduras, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Houghton, MI, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Houma, LA, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Houston, TX, 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Huntington, WV, 1965-1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Huntsville, AL, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Iowa, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Jacksonville, FL, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Jamaica, 1967-1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Jamaica, 1967-1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Jamaica, 1967-1982 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Jamaica, 1967-1982 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Jamaica, 1967-1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Jeffersonville, IN, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Joliet, IL, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Kenosha, WI, 1964-1984 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Keokuk, IA, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Kingston, NY, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Kingston, Ontario, Canada, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Kittanning, PA, 1968-1979 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - LaCrosse, WI, 1964-1987 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Lafayette, LA, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Lake Charleston, LA, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Lancaster, Williamsport, and Harrisburg, PA, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Latrobe, PA, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Lawrenceville (Pittsburgh), PA, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Leland, MI, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Lewisburg, PA, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Long Beach, NY, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Louisiana, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Lorain, OH, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Louisville, KY, 1966-1982 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Mackinac Island, MI, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Madison, IN, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Manitowoc, WI, 1964-1979 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Marietta, OH, 1965-1970 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Mars, PA, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Martins Ferry, OH, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Martinique, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Marquette University (WI), 1973-1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Maysville, KY, 1964-1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - McKeesport, PA, 1962-1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Medina, NY, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Memphis, TN, 1960-1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Menominee and Marinette, WI, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Michigan City, IN, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miami, FL, 1967-1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Mid-Mon Valley, PA, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Middletown, CT, 1975-1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Milwaukee, WI, 1964-1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Minneapolis and St. Paul, MN, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Mobile, AL, 1974-1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Monaca, PA, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Montgomery, WV, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Morgan City, LA, 1983-1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Morgantown, WV, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Monongahela, PA, 1969-1980 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Monroe, MI, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Monroeville, PA, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Mt. Lebanon - Keynotes, PA, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Mt. Vernon, IN, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Muscatine, IA, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Muskegon, MI, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Naples, FL, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Nashville, TN, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Nassau, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Natchez, MS, 1961-1967 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Neenah, WI, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - New England, No Date (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - New Martinsville, WV, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1959-1988 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1959-1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - New Rochelle, NY, 85 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - New York, 1979-1987 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - North Side (Pittsburgh, PA), 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Nicaragua, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Norwalk, CT, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Oak Ridge, TN, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Oakmont, PA, 1966-1981 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Oshkosh, WI, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Oshland, WI, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Owensboro, KY, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Paducah, KY, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Parkersburg, WV, 1962-1973 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Palm Beach, FL, No Date (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Panama, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Panama City, FL, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Pascagoula, MS, 1967-1981 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Pekin, IL, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Pensacola, FL, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Peoria, IL, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Peru, IL, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Petoskey, MI, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Pittsburgh, PA Metro Area, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Pleasant Hills Borough, Pittsburgh, PA, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Point Pleasant, WV, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Pomeroy, OH, 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Port Arthur, TX, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Port Huron, MI, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Port Lavaca, TX, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Port Hope, Ontario, Canada, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Portsmouth, NH, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Portsmouth, OH, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Portsmouth, VA, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rico, 1978-1982 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico, 1978-1982 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Puerto Rico, 1978-1982 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Punta Gorda, FL, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Racine, WI, 1964-1979 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Ravenswood, WV, 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Red Wing, MN, 1962-1986 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Rices Landing, PA, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Richmond, VA, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - RIDC Industrial Park, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - River Tour, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - River Tour, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - River Tour, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - River Tour, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - River Tour, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - River Tour, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rochester, MI, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Rock Island, IL, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rogers City, MI, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Saginaw, MI, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Salem, MA, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Salisbury, MD, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Samford, CT, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Sarnia, Ontario, Canada, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Savannah, GA, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Savannah, TN, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Saybrook, CT, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady, NY, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Seneca Falls, NY, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Sewickley, PA, 1973-1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sharpsburg, PA, No Date (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sheboygan, WI, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Sisterville, WV, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Somerset, PA, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - South Hampton, NY, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - South Padre Island, TX, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - South Side (Pittsburgh, PA), 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Southwest, PA, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Spain, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - St. Adams, WV, 1963-1968 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - St. Augustine, FL, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - St. Joesph, MI, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - St. Louis, MO, 1963-1982 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - St. Marys, MD, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - St. Marys, WV, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - St. Petersburg, FL, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - St. Thomas, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - St. Thomas, St. Croix, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Steubenville, PA, 1966-1980 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Stillwater, MN, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Stratford, CT, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Sturgeon Bay, WI, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Sweden, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Frame 36)
  - Swissvale, PA, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Tallahassee, FL, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Tampa, FL, 1967-1988 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Tarentum, PA, 1964-1970 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Tawas City, MI, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Tennessee, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Texas, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Three Rivers Arts Festival (Pittsburgh,PA), 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Toledo, OH, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Tarentum, Ontario, Canada, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Traverse City, MI, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Trenton, Ontario, Canada, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Trinidad, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Trois Rivieres, Quebec, Canada, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Tuscaloosa, AL, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Uniontown, PA, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - University + City Ministries, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Utica, NY, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Venezuela, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Vicksburg, MS, 1961-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Washington, DC, 1966-1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Washington, DC, 1966-1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Washington, NC, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Washington, PA, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Watertown, NY, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Waukegan, IL, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Welland, Ontario, Canada, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Westchester, NY, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - West Mifflin, PA, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - West Palm Beach, FL, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Westerly, RI, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Wheeling, WV, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Wierton, WV, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Wilkinsburg, PA, No Date (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Wilmington, NC, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Windsor, Ontario, Canada, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Wilmington, NC, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Winona, MN, 1963-1984 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - World Tour, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Photographic Materials, 1954-1981; X.
  This series contains photographs, slides, contact sheets, and negatives that depict AWSO's performances, guest artists, tours, and performance venues. Many photos are promotional shots from professional photographers, though there are some amateur photographs included, as well. There are many photographs of Robert Boudreau, AWSO's conductor, as well as shots of the ensemble performing, the Point Counterpoint and Point Counterpoint II barges, guest artists, and performance venues. The series has been divided into three subseries. The first contains print photographs of AWSO performers, guest artists, and other people associated with the ensemble; the second contains photogrpahic prints of performances, tours, and of Point Counterpoint I and II; the third contains other photographic formats such as negatives, contact prints, and printing plates.
  - People (Photographic Prints), 1954-c1980; 1.
    This subseries contains images of instrumentalists who played with the AWSO as well as guest artists, performers, and conductors.
    - Bennett, Robert Russell (Composer), c1960 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Bennett, Robert Russell (Composer), 67th Birthday, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Boudreau, Robert Austin (Founder & Conductor), c1960-65 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Boudreau, Robert Austin--Conducting, 1958-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Boudreau, Robert Austin--Piloting the Barge, c1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Boudreau, Robert Austin--Small Groups, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Brass Musicians, 1968, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cellist, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Flautist, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Fox, Siv Cedering (Poet), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Harpist, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Horosko, Michele Soyka (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Houhanner, Alan (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Kozikova, Marcela (Harpist), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Leffler, Merrill (Poet) (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Lundgren, Olav (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Musicians (Photo from Valley News & Dispatch), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Neal, Harold (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Nelson, Oliver (Composer), c 1970 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Purvis, Bill (French Horn) (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Sanborne, Peter (Trombone), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Schmertz, Robert (Architect and Folk Musician), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Snyder, Joan (Oboe), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Snyder, Ron (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Tracey, Paul (folklorist), undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Michael (Actor, with Will Geer), undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified Groups of People, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified Man--Filming, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified People, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Topical (Photographic Prints), 2.
    This subseries contains topical photographs of individual concerts, performances, or tours as well as several images of Point Counterpoint I and Point Counterpoint II.
    - Album, Photographs by S. Worhatch Studio (Pittsburgh), c 1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Alton, IL, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - "The Bicentennial Chicken," Theatre Presentation, c 1976 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Billboard Advertising, c1978 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Charleston, WV, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Children's Free Concert, c 1973 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Concert Advertisement at Point State Park, Pittsburgh, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Concert at Three Rivers Arts Festival, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Fireworks, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Greenwich, CT, Undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Indonesian Gamelan, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - London, England, Unknown (Box 22, Folder 41)